<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Security - Tag - decmaxn</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/tags/security/</link><description>Security - Tag - decmaxn</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</managingEditor><webMaster>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://decmaxn.github.io/tags/security/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two factor authentication for Gmail on Z30 - Blackberry 10</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</guid><description>When I turn on 2 factor authentication with gmail,all my devices like Z30 need some reconfiguration.
You might get this idea that you need to install Goggle Authenticator APP on your phone,and found that there is no native app available in your Blackberry world or Amazon App Store. However you get around it by sideload android apps. How to use Google two-step authentication on Blackberry 10 ask you to install Gauth.</description></item><item><title>IMSS Block Yahoo Group emails after email address changed</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/imss-block-yahoo-group-emails-after-email-address-changed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/imss-block-yahoo-group-emails-after-email-address-changed/</guid><description>Symptoms:User can no longer receive emails from her yahoo groups after she changed her email address. Yahoo group website gives error code for the bounce back, but their support doesn’t reply her for details.&amp;nbsp; The error code is:
Last Bounced Message
Remote host said: 501 Syntax error in parameters or arguments [MAIL_FROM]
From IMSS’s log, I couldn’t find any record of either passed or whatever.
Find Sender Email addressTrend Micro support ask for the sender address, but what user reads xxxx@yahoogroups.</description></item></channel></rss>