<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Mobile - Tag - decmaxn</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/tags/mobile/</link><description>Mobile - Tag - decmaxn</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</managingEditor><webMaster>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://decmaxn.github.io/tags/mobile/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two factor authentication for Gmail on Z30 - Blackberry 10</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</guid><description>When I turn on 2 factor authentication with gmail,all my devices like Z30 need some reconfiguration.
You might get this idea that you need to install Goggle Authenticator APP on your phone,and found that there is no native app available in your Blackberry world or Amazon App Store. However you get around it by sideload android apps. How to use Google two-step authentication on Blackberry 10 ask you to install Gauth.</description></item><item><title>Will emails deleted from BB been deleted from Outlook, and vise versa?</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/will-emails-deleted-from-bb-been-deleted-from-outlook-and-vise-versa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/will-emails-deleted-from-bb-been-deleted-from-outlook-and-vise-versa/</guid><description>Been a Black Berry user for years, I have never paid attention to this question.Well the answer is yes, but if you do a test, you probably won&amp;rsquo;t have time to wait for it happen. Emails on BB and your Outlook will sync over air, but not immediately.
&amp;quot;Reconcile Now&amp;rdquo; will sync two place immediately. So do emails you’ve read on your Black Berry appear read in your Outlook.</description></item><item><title>Multiple Desktop Contact List on BB</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/multiple-desktop-contact-list-on-bb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/multiple-desktop-contact-list-on-bb/</guid><description>Found these wonderful thread about this issue here. I just take the question and answer out for you to read easily. Q: Somehow when I starting syncing my new Storm, I ended up with 3 Desktop Contact Lists - all the same, all with the title of &amp;ldquo;Desktop&amp;rdquo;. Now when I go to Contacts, I have 3 copies of every entry. Anyone know how I can delete a contact list individually without resetting the unit ?</description></item></channel></rss>