<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - decmaxn</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | decmaxn</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</managingEditor><webMaster>victor.ma@gmail.com (Victor Ma)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://decmaxn.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MDT Admin Password</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-admin-password/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-admin-password/</guid><description>This setting alone won't protect you. SkipAdminPassword=YESYou should also include this one. AdminPassword=YourPasswordHowever, there is another way, if you don't want to set all your deployed computer with same password:- When you create the installation TS, one of the step is to set Admin Password.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This admin password will be the local admin password for all deployments with that task sequence. I have so far found it in the following 2 places.</description></item><item><title>Hide Altiris Agent icon from end users, but not admins</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/hide-altiris-agent-icon-from-end-users-but-not-admins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/hide-altiris-agent-icon-from-end-users-but-not-admins/</guid><description><![CDATA[Instruction to hide itYou can find one instruction for version 6, but not 7.5. Her is how:Go to:Settings&nbsp; &nbsp;Agents/Plug-ins&nbsp; &nbsp;Symantec Management Agent&nbsp; &nbsp;Settings&nbsp; &nbsp;Symantec Management Agent Settings - Targeted Choose "User Control" Tab, and uncheck "Show client tray icon". It will disappear on client the next time they update. How to display Altiris Management Agent Settings window from command line
C:\Program Files\Altiris\Altiris Agent\AexAgentActivate.exe ]]></description></item><item><title>Policy for offline computers</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/policy-for-offline-computers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/policy-for-offline-computers/</guid><description>If one computer is online and get the policy, for example install a program every 1 hour 24x7, even it get offline, it will still install it every 1 hour, till the installation is success. After it successfully finishes, it won't run the installation again and again anymore.
However, admin won't be able to see it's success, and the computer will remain in the list of computers without this program, till next time this computer get online and report it's success.</description></item><item><title>FAQ on Wake-On-Lan (WOL)</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/faq-on-wake-on-lan-wol/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/faq-on-wake-on-lan-wol/</guid><description>Here is a really good document to learn about WOL, thanks a lot to Symantec!</description></item><item><title>Win_feature changes will fail the tasks behind it, and it's solution</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/win_feature-changes-will-fail-the-tasks-behind-it-and-its-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/win_feature-changes-will-fail-the-tasks-behind-it-and-its-solution/</guid><description><![CDATA[The problem with these code is, after Server-Gui-Shell, Server-Gui-Mgmt-Infra are uninstalled, the windows will reboot immediately, leaving index.html template deployment failed.&nbsp;vagrant@acs:~/pywinrm$ cat iis.yaml---- hosts: s12&nbsp; tasks:&nbsp; - name: Ensure IIS seb service is installed&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; win_feature:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; name: web-server&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; state: present&nbsp; - name: Ensure Server GUI is not installed&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; win_feature:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; name: Server-Gui-Shell&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; state: absent&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; restart: true&nbsp; - name: Deploy index.html file&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; template:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; src: iisstart.j2You can put that Windows Feature block to the last of this playbook, or use handlers as below.]]></description></item><item><title>Two factor authentication for Gmail on Z30 - Blackberry 10</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/two-factor-authentication-for-gmail-on-z30-blackberry-10/</guid><description>When I turn on 2 factor authentication with gmail,all my devices like Z30 need some reconfiguration.
You might get this idea that you need to install Goggle Authenticator APP on your phone,and found that there is no native app available in your Blackberry world or Amazon App Store. However you get around it by sideload android apps. How to use Google two-step authentication on Blackberry 10 ask you to install Gauth.</description></item><item><title>MDT: unable to mount wim so the update process cannot continue</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-unable-to-mount-wim-so-the-update-process-cannot-continue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-unable-to-mount-wim-so-the-update-process-cannot-continue/</guid><description>MDT installed on Windows 7. The problem is quite simple - permission.
Solution is to run MDT as Administrator.</description></item><item><title>Unable to power on VMs due to expired ESX license</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/unable-to-power-on-vms-due-to-expired-esx-license/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/unable-to-power-on-vms-due-to-expired-esx-license/</guid><description>I knew ESX alone is free. Although I always get &amp;ldquo;License Expired&amp;rdquo; warning at the right bottom of my vSphere, as long as I can still use it, I never thought about fix it. Today I rebooted it after enabled a feature, and found I can no longer power up my VMs, due to license issue. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a chance to take any screen dump. I followed these two posts from https://communities.</description></item><item><title>iLo2: Boot from Virtual Media failed almost all the time</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/ilo2-boot-from-virtual-media-failed-almost-all-the-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/ilo2-boot-from-virtual-media-failed-almost-all-the-time/</guid><description>I have been struggle for a few days for the above mentioned problem. First I thought it&amp;rsquo;s the ISO file&amp;rsquo;s problem, but it failed multiple ISO file for different purpose . Among them ESXi boot ISO files gave consistent error code, I forgot what it is now.
I thought about iLO&amp;rsquo;s KVM problem, connect the real monitor keyboard, failed too. How about firmware? I downloaded HP Service Pack for ProLiant from HP, but booting from this ISO failed too.</description></item><item><title>iLo2: up / down arrow key doesn't work for HP Proliant DL360 G5</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/ilo2-up-down-arrow-key-doesnt-work-for-hp-proliant-dl360-g5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2014 17:17:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/ilo2-up-down-arrow-key-doesnt-work-for-hp-proliant-dl360-g5/</guid><description>This happened when I try to change some BIOS configuration, struggled for a while, and find this configuring ESXi with iLO 2 on bl490c - up/down arrow don't work.Thanks to the poster for the simple solution:&amp;nbsp; Works with the Java-version, but not in the IRC.Some one mentioned turn off IE protection mode also could solve the problem, but I didn't bother to try it.&amp;nbsp;</description></item></channel></rss>