<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Victor Ma</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Victor Ma</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:16:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://decmaxn.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Homebrew Tap</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/homebrew-tap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/homebrew-tap/</guid><description><![CDATA[Homebrew Tap Currently I have only 3 taps
1 2 3 4  % brew tap homebrew/cask homebrew/cask-versions homebrew/core   When searching, the results are from those 3 taps.
1 2 3 4 5 6  % brew search aws-sam-cli ==&gt; Formulae aws-sam-cli aws-sso-cli ==&gt; Casks aws-vpn-client   Let&rsquo;s add another Tap, it&rsquo;s from AWS.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7  % brew tap aws/tap Running `brew update --auto-update`.]]></description></item><item><title>Devcontainer Space Issue</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/devcontainer-space-issue/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 17:53:32 -0400</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/devcontainer-space-issue/</guid><description>Failed to start devcontainer - no space left on device When this happen, open &amp;ldquo;Docker Desktop&amp;rdquo; GUI console and clean up useless Images or Containers. But this way wil run into an end, like this time.
First of all, df -H to make sure you have enough free space
已经都删干净了啊， Docker 系统中有 3 个镜像，3 个容器，8 个本地数据卷和 423 个构建缓存文件。
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 $ docker system df TYPE TOTAL ACTIVE SIZE RECLAIMABLE Images 3 3 4.</description></item><item><title>Interactive Login and Non Login Shell</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/interactive-login-and-non-login-shell/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:32 -0400</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/interactive-login-and-non-login-shell/</guid><description>TL;DR .bash_profile 和 .bashrc 文件包含在 Bash shell 启动时要运行的 shell 命令。.bash_profile 文件在交互式登录 shell 中被读取和执行，而.bashrc 文件在非登录 shell 中被读取和执行。
.profile 文件是一个针对 Unix shell（如 bash、sh、ksh 等）的配置文件。当使用 Unix shell 登录时，它会在用户主目录下寻找并执行该文件。与 .bash_profile特定于 bash shell不同，.profile 文件适用于多种 Unix shell，因此具有更广泛的适用性。
vscode In vscode, the terminal wil run .profile, which will call .bashrc. So let&amp;rsquo;s put all command completers or PATH in .bashrc
SHELL 交互式和非交互式 登录和非登录 在 Unix/Linux 系统中，有 交互式（interactive）和非交互式 两种 shell。
交互式是指可以从终端或命令行界面中输入和接收命令的 shell。 非交互式没有终端，比如运行一个脚本时。 交互式 shell有两种类型：登录 shell 和非登录 shell。下面详细介绍交互式登录和非登录 shell 的概念。</description></item><item><title>Bare_metal_linux</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/bare_metal_linux/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 20:16:51 -0500</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/bare_metal_linux/</guid><description>UEFI bios and Linux Server Installing Linux server on HP Desktop with UEFI feature. Expensive lessson I have learned:
Everytime installation failed after it start to copy files, I have tested all kinds of different ways, and it turn out the problem is UEFI.
Updated the the next day: The problem wasn&amp;rsquo;t solved this way, I just installed Ubuntu Desktop, that solved the problem.
1 From BIOS -&amp;gt; Boot Order, you can disable the whole UEFI feature here Modifications after install Change IP address with netplan When installing the OS, I choosed DHCP.</description></item><item><title>Thankyou_cloud</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/thankyou_cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 23:43:14 -0500</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/thankyou_cloud/</guid><description>Thank you, Cloud. Started to learn go, I feel that I have to review my Kubernetes (K8s) skills. Cloned my old K8s Lab repo, starting up the lab environment using VirtualBox and Vagrant, I thought it would be like riding a bike.
However, things didn&amp;rsquo;t go as smoothly as I had hoped. I spent hours struggling to make things work with current versions of everything, which is expected. After that the same laptop doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as good as before, encountering errors left and right, waiting there for CPU to come down to normal, worrying that my old laptop might be too dirty, that the high temperature is slowing down it mor and feeling completely out of my depth.</description></item><item><title>Downgrade_virtualbox_for_vagrant</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/downgrade_virtualbox_for_vagrant/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 16:02:13 -0500</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/downgrade_virtualbox_for_vagrant/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade virtualbox to the latest when work with vagrant Check Vagrant official Doc for compatible version of Virtualbox. I have found misleading information from other places.
Now I have to downgrade Virtualbox. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 # Uninstall current version of virtualbox 7 choco uninstall virtualbox # Search available versions choco search virtualbox --exact --all-versions # Install a compatible version choco install virtualbox --version=6.</description></item><item><title>Git_controlled_doc_on_confluence</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/git_controlled_doc_on_confluence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:45:11 -0500</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/git_controlled_doc_on_confluence/</guid><description>Why Git can be used for managing changes to other types of files, such as documents. For documents related to code and infra, Confluence can be just a publshing system, while the Version tracking, Collaboration, Branching and Backup happens at Git side.
There should be a CICD pipeline to deploy changes to Confluence.
Instruction Confluence Publisher can be used for this purpose. Refer to it&amp;rsquo;s Github for details.
Also Docker Image seems to be updated recently as well.</description></item><item><title>git_under_the_hood</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/git_under_the_hood/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 15:05:13 -0500</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/git_under_the_hood/</guid><description><![CDATA[Meet SHA1 Every Object in Git has its own SHA1. SHA1 are unique in the universe?!
 This cryptograph concept and technology is also used for bitcoin.
 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19  :~$ mkdir gitdemo :~$ cd gitdemo/ :~/gitdemo$ echo &#34;Apple Pie&#34; | git hash-object --stdin # Create a SHA1. 23991897e13e47ed0adb91a0082c31c82fe0cbe5 :~/gitdemo$ echo &#34;Apple Pie&#34; | git hash-object --stdin -w # -w write it to GIT repository.]]></description></item><item><title>MDT Admin Password</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-admin-password/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:27:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/mdt-admin-password/</guid><description>This setting alone won't protect you. SkipAdminPassword=YESYou should also include this one. AdminPassword=YourPasswordHowever, there is another way, if you don't want to set all your deployed computer with same password:- When you create the installation TS, one of the step is to set Admin Password.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This admin password will be the local admin password for all deployments with that task sequence. I have so far found it in the following 2 places.</description></item><item><title>Hide Altiris Agent icon from end users, but not admins</title><link>https://decmaxn.github.io/hide-altiris-agent-icon-from-end-users-but-not-admins/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Victor Ma</author><guid>https://decmaxn.github.io/hide-altiris-agent-icon-from-end-users-but-not-admins/</guid><description><![CDATA[Instruction to hide itYou can find one instruction for version 6, but not 7.5. Her is how:Go to:Settings&nbsp; &nbsp;Agents/Plug-ins&nbsp; &nbsp;Symantec Management Agent&nbsp; &nbsp;Settings&nbsp; &nbsp;Symantec Management Agent Settings - Targeted Choose "User Control" Tab, and uncheck "Show client tray icon". It will disappear on client the next time they update. How to display Altiris Management Agent Settings window from command line
C:\Program Files\Altiris\Altiris Agent\AexAgentActivate.exe ]]></description></item></channel></rss>